SHAWN (SUNGWOONG) PYEON

57 Forest Avenue, Hamilton, ON, L8N 1X3 | P.: 905-966-9703 | E.: tjddnd523@gmail.com | W.: goo.gl/ofuQqS

PROFILE

A driven, high-spirited second year Computer Systems Technician – Software student at Mohawk College with extensive computer skills. Possesses organizational and problem-solving skills as well as vast knowledge in programming, social media platforms and internet applications. Possess experience from numerous projects through running blogs, using Instagram, building websites and working with other modern outlets. Ability to organize, create marketing strategies. Excellent team player with strong connections and previous volunteer experience. Able to quickly adapt to any required role.

CORE COMPETENCIES

Java
HTML & CSS
Relationship Building
Organizational Skills

JavaScript & PHP
Workload Prioritization
Multicultural Awareness
MS Office Suite

Python
Problem-Solving
Decision Making
Bilingual: Korean & English

EXPERIENCE

Student Ambassador (Volunteer)

2017 - Present

Mohawk College – International and Partnerships, Hamilton, ON

- Assisted new internationals students with registration and course selection
- Offered information to students regarding their accounts, courses, health insurance and bus passes
- Provided campus tours to new international students

Team Member 2018 - Present

Mo's Golden Pretzel, Hamilton, ON

- Greeted customers with urgency, eye contact, sincerity, thoughtful closing and smile/voice inflection
- Accurately operated cash registers in accordance with cash register procedures

Art Gallery Attendant

2018 - Present

Assembly Gallery, Hamilton, ON

- Introduced customers to the artwork displayed in the gallery and answered any general questions about artists and other exhibits
- Handled payments and completed transactions of sold artworks to customers

Server 2017 - 2018

Bulgogi BBQ, Hamilton, ON

- Greeted patrons, presented menus, made recommendations and answered questions regarding food and beverages
- Served food, beverages and presented bills to patrons and accepted payment

EDUCATION